The magic and madness of making Apocalypse Now
Hearts of Darkness: A Filmmaker's Apocalypse is a
documentary film directed by George Hickenlooper.
A chronicle of the production problems — including bad weather, actors' health, war near the filming locations, and more — which
plagued the filming of Apocalypse Now, increasing costs and nearly destroying the life and career of Francis Ford Coppola.
Self, played by Francis Ford Coppola.
Self, played by Eleanor Coppola.
Self, played by John Milius.
Self, played by George Lucas.
Self, played by Sam Bottoms.
Self, played by Albert Hall.
Hearts of Darkness: A Filmmaker's Apocalypse is a 1991 American documentary film by Fax Bahr and George Hickenlooper
about the production of Apocalypse Now, a 1979 Vietnam War epic directed by Francis Ford Coppola.
The film explores themes of movie business,
philippines, behind the scenes, madness, ego.